<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on CatWorld</title><link>http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on CatWorld</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 16:09:16 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Felines Flip for Catnip</title><link>http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/why-felines-flip-for-catnip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 16:09:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/why-felines-flip-for-catnip/</guid><description>If you’ve ever watched as a cat “flipped” over fresh Catnip perhaps you’ve been struck with the question; “what causes Catnip to affect cats that way?” Catnip is indeed an unusual phenomenon among cats, it has the ability to alter your cat’s behavior like nothing else can.
So what exactly is the reason for what scientists have coined as “The Catnip Effect”?
Unfortunately for such inquisitive minds the exact reason of why Catnip affects cats in such a manner remains mostly a mystery.</description></item><item><title>Kibble Science – How it’s Made</title><link>http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/kibble-science-how-its-made/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 16:09:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/kibble-science-how-its-made/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered how your cat’s kibble (dry food) is made? If so, we thought you might find the science behind it interesting. We certainly did! ^..^&amp;lt;
Take a walk thru your local pet store and you’ll see dozens of different kibble brands to choose from available in shapes ranging from tiny balls, squares, triangles and even animal shapes like fish or chicken.
Have you ever wondered how your cat’s kibble (dry food) is made?</description></item><item><title>The Cat – A Natural and Cultural History</title><link>http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/the-cat-a-natural-and-cultural-history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 16:09:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://mrtejas99.github.com/posts/the-cat-a-natural-and-cultural-history/</guid><description>We were so excited to come across this remarkable new book called The Cat ~ it’s a comprehensive, richly illustrated exploration of the natural and cultural history of this much-loved pet. Filled with surprising facts, The Cat will enchant anyone with an interest in, or a love for, these ameowzing animals.
This is truly a quintessential ‘must have’ reference book for any ailurophile (cat lover) that features clear and accessible text plus infographics, diagrams, and some 250 stunning color photographs.</description></item></channel></rss>